Hi Good day This is Jane of sunlife and
today we will discuss one of the best
Plan Perfect for retirement but of
course there are also other plans that
we can you can get for retirement
purposes so but for for today we will
discuss an accelerate This is only This
is a limited payment um option plan that
you can get for only 8 years to pay
through annual semi-annual or quarterly
mode and the coverage is 20 years so
After 20 years this policy is mature So
why It's The Best For Me for retirement
because for example a 37 year old female
took it so by age 57 she will get the
um benefits of this plan so the
annual I did for her is
74,000 her face amount but the
um Deb benefit of this is increasing
yearly so for
example this is um so year 1 350,000 year
two 406 year 3 and so forth until
year 21.4 million her
life insurance coverage
So aside from that that's why this is the
good retirement plan the
total will be lower  The client will pay
584,284 over 8 years so since it stopped, that's
584,284 but the possible amount
he can get after maturity is
[Music]
1,186 this is what is called the total living
benefit so this is the total living
benefit. Okay, so that's
1.14,186. That's why it became that. I
added more or less. I can
get it. I added
the non-guaranteed illustrative
accumulated special paid of bonus of
6,999. Sun Life is giving it so
this is the first time it has given after a
year of the policy and then that's it.
If you don't take it, you apply
to the endowment and you can
just keep it with Sunlife. It can grow and it
can be
your total. So that's it. And then this
policy also has a guaranteed cash value since this is a
participating policy. It also has a
guaranteed cash value so that's
37,000. So that's what I added, so it became a
million. That's what the client can take
when the policy matures.  plan so he will earn
more or less
4299 this is what he can earn in
um 20 years so that's it while
um while he is insured So
his money is also saved which he can use
for retirement so this one is one of
the best plan that we can offer for
retirement so there you go So if interested
you can also increase the premium so that
the
um is even bigger so that it can be used
for
retirement So if you have any questions
Please Don't hesitate to message me
Thank you for what Ching